THARINDU DAMITH HASHANTHA

SUMMARY

I'm a hard-working and enthusiastic individual with selfmotivation, good communication skills and have been gathered much enough experience and knowledge through self-studying, who use Information Technology and Computer Science in the best possible manner to achieve any goal.

EDUCATION

University Of Sri Jayewardenenpura – 2017 to Present B.Sc. PHYSICAL SCIENCE ICT

Mo/Kumaradasa Vidyalaya – 2016

G.C.E ADVANCED LEVEL

INFORMATION & COMMUNICATION TECH. - C
COMBINED MATHEMATICS - C
PHYSICS - S

Mo/Hingurukaduwa Vidyalaya – 2012

G.C.E ORDINARY LEVEL

5 A Passes

2 B Passes

2 C Passes

Front End Developer

WORK EXPERIENCE

CodeGen International(Pvt) Ltd	2013(Jan-May)
 Former Web Developer Foundation Of Goodness 	2016 - 2017
IT Teacher in Lak Aruna Foundation	2010 2017
Apium Innovation(Pvt) Ltd	2018 – 2020
· ·	2018 - 2020
Apium Innovation(Pvt) Ltd • Associate Software Engineer • Saleforce Developer Productive Media	2018 - 2020 2018 - 2020

SKILLS

Language: C, Java, Python, Dart, Javascript, HTML, SCSS, Nodejs, Angular, PHP, SQL, Mathematica, MATLAB

IDE : VS Code, CodeBlocks, Netbeans, Android Studio, Arduino

Database: MS Access, MySQL, Firebase, MongoDB



Contact

- +(94)71-4669-150
- <u>A Hingurukaduwa, Passara</u>
- M tharindud02@gmail.com
- in /tharindu-damith-39349650/
- /tharindud02/

Additional Skills

- Computer Skills
- Leadership
- Problem-solving
- CommunicationTeamwork
- Coorto
- Sports

Interest

- Coding
- Movies
- Sports
- Music
- Travelling

PROJECTS

Wild Apricot Membership Project for IESL: CodeGen International (Pvt)

Apium Web: Apium Innovations (Pvt)

Saleforce Development : Apium Innovations (Pvt)

Fonteva: Apium Innovations (Pvt)

Kamudha Mobile App : Apium Innovations (Pvt)

Packbook System: Apium Innovations (Pvt)

Essexaesthetics Web: Productive Media

SEOFulham Web: Productive Media

Funesoft Web: Productive Media

iCart Smart Shopping App: University Sri Jayewardenepura

Smart Traffic Light System: University Sri Jayewardenepura

Self Eco Tester: University Sri Jayewardenepura

Empty Seat Detector: University Sri Jayewardenepura

Data Mining in E-Learning Research: University Sri Jayewardenepura

ACHEIVEMENTS

Microsoft Presentation Competition: 3rd(2010) Place,

3rd and 5th (2011) Places

Long Jump in Divisional Level : 3rd Place

NON RELATED REFERENCE

Mr. Chamth Nimantha Founder in Apium Innvations linkedin.com/in/chamathme chamath2007@gmail.com +9478-3477915 Himanshi Liyanage Lecturer in IT, University of Sri Jayawardenapura Bsc.(SL), Msc (poland), PhD (reading), himanshi@sip.ac.lk

DECLARATION

I do hereby certify that the above particulars are true and accurate to the best of my knowledge.

| R T D HASHANTHA